rapbasement.com 2012-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Features | Rap Basement

Rap Basement is committed to protecting your personal information and respecting your privacy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make use of Rap Basement's offerings and services. The following describes Rap Basement's information gathering and dissemination practices. To obtain information regarding the privacy policy of any of our affiliated web sites, please check directly with that web site. Rap Basementhas no control over the policies of its affiliated web sites. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. In general, you can visit Rap Basement on the web without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Rap Basement will never sell, rent, trade, loan or disclose your personally identifiable information to outside parties without your consent unless compelled by law or court order to do so. If you purchase a product or a service developed or owned by a third party through our website, we may provide to the product owner or the licensor the same information you provide to us. We may share non-personal, summary, or aggregate customer data with partners and other third parties. With your permission, Rap Basement may send you e-mail regarding our new products, upgrades available through our site, or select third party products.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use DoubleClick, Gorilla Nation, and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx). For more information about Gorilla Nation, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please [click here](http://gorillanation.com/privacy/).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To "opt-out," please click here. http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx. 

We partner with third party ad networks and allow such networks to use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable data for targeting and serving ads. Users can opt-out of this behavioral targeting by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

**Information We Collect & Our Policy**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). 

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations and the email address, location, gender and other information used to create your profile on community.rapbasement.com. 

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site , ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or updating your profile settings in community.rapbasement.com or board.rapbasement.com. 

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board. 

From time to time, we make our _customer_ e-mail list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board. 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board. 

you may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board. 

Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizationa 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by , visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board. 

Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations 

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: [Double Click](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy) , [Gorilla Nation](http://gorillanation.com/privacy/) and [Flux](http://www.socialproject.com/PrivacyPolicy.html)

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board.. 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to no information that we have collected and that we maintain about them. 

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. 

Consumers can have this information corrected by visiting us at <http://community.rapbasement.com/-/Signup.aspx> or Updating your profile on the appropriate message board, community tool or other assets in the RapBasement.com network. 

**With respect to security** : We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact state or local consumer protection office or contact flux.com support for community.rapbasement.com or an administrator of our message board or contacting flux.com . 

**Your Acceptance of this Policy**

By using this site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not access our site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change modify, add or remove portions of or the entire policy at any time. Your continued use of our site following the posting of any such changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
